Don Wright Papers
Don Wright Papers
1963-1968
Wright, Don, 1934-
4.8 linear ft.
Over 500 original editorial cartoons from approximately 1963-1968 and correspondence (1963-1965) with related clippings.
2655705
Biographical History
Donald Conway Wright (1934- ), professionally known as Don Wright, is an American editorial cartoonist who won the Pulitzer Prize in 1966 and 1980.
Don Wright was born January 23, 1934, in Los Angeles, California. When he was a child, his family moved across the country to Florida and he graduated from Miami Edison High School in 1952. Wright's interest in cartoons began when he took a job as copyboy with the Miami News (1952-1956). Although the News refused to move Wright to the art department, on the grounds he probably would be drafted from that job, they did allow him to become a photographer. Wright was subsequently drafted, served in the U.S. Army as a photographer and ultimately returned to the Miami News as graphics editor in December 1958.
Shortly after his rejoining the News, Wright resigned. Not wishing to lose Wright however, the News offered, as a compromise, to publish some of his cartoons. By 1963 Wright had transformed the original one or two cartoons per week, on local issues, into a regular appearance on the editorial page.
Wright won his first Pulitzer Prize for editorial cartooning in 1966 for his cartoon titled "You Mean You Were Bluffing?". He won the award again in 1980. Wright has also been recognized with the National Headliners Club Award (1969, 1972, 1980, 1982) and is a two-time winner of the Distinguished Service Award from Sigma Delta Chi. Wright has won five awards from the Overseas Press Club and he received a Robert F. Kennedy journalism award in 1983. The National Cartoonists Society named Wright the best editorial cartoonist in 1985. His work has been collected in the books Wright On! A Collection of Political Cartoons (1971) and Wright Side Up (1981).
His work has been syndicated by the Washington (DC) Star Syndicates and the New York Times Syndicate. In 1989, Wright moved to the Palm Beach Post, where he remained until his retirement in August 2008. As of 2009 he continues to draw cartoons distributed by Tribune Media Services.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Don Wright Papers are divided into two series. Cartoons contains approximately 527 original editorial cartoons. Some cartoons are dated (1964-1965) while the remainder are undated and from approximately 1963 to 1968.
The cartoons were drawn with ink and crayon on illustration board. Traces of pencil are visible. The majority of the captions are typed on paper and taped onto the cartoons. Generally, the cartoons are two sizes. The majority are approximately 11" x 14" although there are some smaller cartoons. There are also 38 oversize cartoons with image sizes of 8 ½" x 11 ½" mounted on board measuring 16" x 20".
Prevalent in the collection are Wright's caricatures of president Lyndon B. Johnson and 1964 presidential candidate Barry Goldwater as well as cartoons focused on the Republican Party, the Vietnam War, and the civil rights movement in the American South. Wright routinely criticized the actions of Southern segregationists and offered bold depictions critical of the Ku Klux Klan and the anti-communist John Birch Society. Cartoons about local issues and Florida governor Haydon Burns are also included.
Correspondence (1963-1965) contains primarily incoming letters from readers (including several children), politicians and representatives of various publications and organizations. Typical subjects are requests for copies of cartoons and notes of praise and criticism.
Controversial cartoons discussed in the correspondence include those related to the John Birch Society, Barry Goldwater and the law enforcement involved in the civil rights movement. Of particular interest are several items from readers alleging that Wright's work supported communism as well as clippings of cartoons from the paper on which the readers drew and/or voiced their disagreement in ink. Several letters in this tone stemmed from a controversial cartoon (March 9, 1965) in which Wright criticized the Alabama State Troopers for their treatment of civil rights activists.
There is also one signed letter from Barry Goldwater (1963) and a note from cartoonist Syd Hoff.
Arrangement of the Collection
Dated editorial cartoons are arranged in chronological order and foldered by month. Undated cartoons are arranged in alphabetical order by caption. Correspondence is arranged in chronological order.
Related Material
has collections of over one hundred cartoonists. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Burns, Haydon, 1912-1987 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Gaulle, Charles de, 1890-1970 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Goldwater, Barry M. (Barry Morris), 1909-1998 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Kennedy, Robert F., 1925-1968 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Spock, Benjamin, 1903-1998 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Wallace, George C. (George Corley), 1919-1998 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Wright, Don, 1934- -- Archives.; John Birch Society -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Ku Klux Klan (1915- ) -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ) -- Caricatures and cartoons.; United States. Congress -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Miami news.; Art -- Cartoonists; American wit and humor, Pictorial.; Caricatures and cartoons -- Florida.; Caricatures and cartoons -- United States.; Cartoonists -- Florida.; Cartoonists -- United States.; Civil rights movements -- United States -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Editorial cartoons -- Florida.; Editorial cartoons -- United States.; Pulitzer Prizes.; Southern States -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Space Exploration -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Vietnam War, 1961-1975 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; World politics -- 1945-1989 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; United States -- Politics and government -- 1963-1969 -- Caricatures and cartoons.; Cartoons (humorous images); Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Editorial cartoons.; Cartoonists.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Don Wright 1964, 1968.
Inventory
- Cartoons
  - Dated
    - Feb 1964 (Oversize 1)
      Feb 6- I Can hardly Hear Myself Figure Their application for More Foreign Aid: foreign aid
    - Dec 1964 (Oversize 1)
      Dec 2- I Think He Agrees With Me On Why Rates Are Going Up: auto insurance
      Dec 6- Take Me To A Leader: Republican Party
      Dec 10- I Christen Thee: NATO, nuclear weapons
      Dec 13- [Four-Part Cartoon w/ two men talking]: Peace Corps, Mississippi
      Dec 16- Tell The Air Force It Just Keeps Coming: Robert McNamara
      Dec 20- Drought: Dean Burch, Barry Goldwater
      Dec 21- If We Need Anything Else From You Foreigners, We'll Say So: Vietnam War causalities, Nguyen Khanh
      Dec 23- Eclipse: King Orange
      Dec 30- —Er, Whose Little Boy Are You?: Haydon Burns, Florida, education
      Dec 31- C'mon Somebody — One Last Fling: holiday traffic fatalities
    - Jan 1965 (Oversize 1)
      Jan 4- Takeoff: Congo, Cuba, China, Vietnam, Indonesia
      Jan 5- Want To See Some Tricks?: Congress
      Jan 6- Tell Me It Isn't A Mirage: Florida, Dade County
      Jan 7- Follow Me!: Sukarno
      Jan 10 - —Winter Playground For Celebrities Such As Jackie Gleason, Robert Goulet, Jimmy Durante, Murph the Surf--: Miami Beach
      Jan 12- It's No Use—He's Going to Pull Through: Medicare
      Jan 14- [Elephant standing in doorway point at Barry Goldwater]: Barry Goldwater
      Jan 15- Pppphhhhtttttttt!: city politician
      Jan 19- [General Assembly United Nations]: U. Thant
      Jan 20- [Lyndon Johnson as a shooting star]:
      Jan 21- Isn't It Just Too Bad About Where The Liberals Are Going?: anti-communist Christian crusade
      Jan 24- Southern Bell Rate Hearings: telephone industry
      Jan 25- Carry on, and dread nought: Winston Churchill
      Jan 26- —So I Said To Myself, 'Are You Going To Be A Small-Time Cold Bug All Your Life?: illness, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Jan 27- Ah Like 'Em Tight, Don't You?: national debt, budget, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Jan 28- [Aerojet General Solid Rocket Fuel Testing Chamber]
      Jan 31- [State Insurance Commissioner]: insurance industry
    - Feb 1965 (Oversize 1)
      Feb 3- What's It Worth?
      Feb 4- Where'd My People Go?
      Feb 7- Of Course, When I Pass On Here, I Will Bring You Many New Proposals, Which Will Mean You Must Revamp Your Entire System These Changes Will Correct A Fundamental–
      Feb 10- [Mao Lighting Fuse To Southeast Asia]: Mao Zedong, Asia
      Feb 12- [Lasso around a U.S. Dollar with wings]: European and South American countries
      Feb 13- [Uncle Sam carrying a U.S. soldier in Vietnam]: Vietnam War
      Feb 16- The Four R's: teachers
      Feb 17- Hey! Watch Where I'm Leading Us!: China, Alexey Kosygin
      Feb 18- [Airport Car Rental Concession]
      Feb 19- [Bullseye on the Moon]: space exploration
      Feb 21- [headless man "Saigon" walks around]
      Feb 23- Death Of A Salesman: Malcolm X, violence
      Feb 24- [Collapsed Sugar Market]: Fidel Castro
      Feb 25- Ach! Der Hussy!: Ludwig Erhard, William J. Fulbright
      Feb 26- [X-Way Designers]
      Feb 28- [What your Government is doing]: press
    - Mar 1965 (Oversize 1)
      Mar 2- Negotiate: Vietnam War
      Mar 3- ['Come see us, Podnuh ' LBJ - 'Dear Lyndon: You'd Love Moscow ' Alexei"]: Alexey Kosygin
      Mar 4- Burp!: politics, regents
      Mar 5- Haydon, Something About Us Makes Him Nervous: Haydon Burns, press
      Mar 7- [Watchdogs for Americanism Blacklist]: communism
      Mar 9- Evolution: Alabama state troopers
      Mar 10- [Governor Alabama]: George Wallace
      Mar 16- —Just Lying Around, Cooling It How Goes It With You, Alexei?: Nikita Khrushchev, Alexey Kosygin
      Mar 21- He Says we BOTH have to let him up: Lyndon B. Johnson, civil rights
      Mar 21- Raise? I Thought They Said Raze!: Supreme Court, Congress
      Mar 24- [Astronaut in spaceship looks at footprints in space]: space exploration
      Mar 24- [Honest That Gas we're sending to Vietnam is harmless stuff It's only used to control riots Honest, Nothing to it at all]: Lyndon B. Johnson, world opinion
      Mar 25- [Briefing NASA]: space exploration
      Mar 30- Haw! With Our Roles Off, How They Gonna Know Us?: Ku Klux Klan, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Mar 31- [Ambassador Maxwell D Taylor returned Sunday for a week of consultations with 'a feeling that things are turning for the better' in Vietnam]: Vietnam War
    - Apr 1965 (Oversize 1)
      Apr 4- Slaves: smoking
      Apr 6- [Reapportionment]: Florida legislature
      Apr 7- Washboard Road: Soviet Union, France, Britain
      Apr 8- Let Us Now Assume We Have Only 49 States: Martin Luther King, Jr.
      Apr 9- Amour: Florida, Dade County
      Apr 13- Old Faithful: Congress, education, Medicare, Appalachia, voting rights
      Apr 14- Early Spring Blossom (Dickipoodus Candidatus Prospectus): Richard Nixon
      Apr 15- [TFX]: defense spending
      Aor 18- Easter Lily: voting rights
      Apr 19- He Just Keeps Rollin' Along!: flooding
      Apr 21- [Man looks up at a rain drop]: weather
      Apr 22- We Hunger To Help Our Little Neighbors: Mao Zedong
      Apr 23- Guided Missile: Medicare
      Apr 24- [Person wearing an oversized helmet]: Dominican Republic
      Apr 25- [Big Steel]: Lyndon B. Johnson, steel industry
      Apr 27- Tallahassee Maniac: Florida legislature, Dade County, price fixing
      Apr 28- Horrors! Bad Enough We're In A War—Now You're Trying To Win It: Wayne Morse, Vietnam War
      Apr 30- [Shastri surrounded by Peking and Pakistan sharks]: China, Pakistan, Lal Bahadur Shastri
    - May 1965 (Oversize 1)
      May 2- Nothing Will Come Between Us: Dominican Republic, democracy
      May 4- [Castro under a gun marked "USMC"]: Dominican Republic, Fidel Castro, armed forces
      May 5- Gee. A Little Something For Everybody: political ideologies
      May 6- [Statue of Liberty with a larger muscle]
      May 10- [Dominican Revolution]: Dominican Republic, Juan Bosch
      May 11- [Charles De Gaulle]: SEATO, NATO, foreign policy, U.S. Dollar, common market
      May 12- Fly in the Soup: poll tax, voting rights
      May 13- [Everglades National Park]: flooding
      May 16- [Organization of American States as a turtle]: Lyndon B. Johnson
      May 18- Relax He Doesn't Know How To Throw It Yet: nuclear weapons, China
      May 19- He's An Accused Murderer: organized labor, right to work laws
      May 20- Ask That One Near The End For His Autograph: Ku Klux Klan
      May 23- Op Art: Lyndon B. Johnson, Dominican Republic
      May 25- Can't Stand Looking At Yourself, Eh?: Congress, Bobby Baker
      May 26- [Lyndon Johnson with multiple arms and hands pointing different directions]
      May 27- [White Only voting booth]: voting rights, Congress
      May 31- [John Lindsay holding an elephant]: Republican Party
    - Jun 1965 (Oversize 1)
      Jun 1- Now Folks, The Next Act On 'Let's See You Top This!: space exploration
      Jun 4- Who Ever Heard Of A Master, Master Sargent?: Sargent Shriver, poverty, Peace Corps, Congress
      Jun 6- Issues! Issues!: Republican Party
      Jun 8- Doesn't It Bother You That None Return To Roost?: peace, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Jun 10- I'd Swear That Thing Was Getting Around?: space exploration
      Jun 11- Anybody See A Place To Turn Around?: Vietnam War
      Jun 13- [Robert Wagner and John Lindsay holding on to stars over New York City]
      Jun 15- Hit 'Em Again, Hit 'Em Again, Harder, Harder—: Vietnam War, Barry Goldwater
      Jun 16- Boo!: stock market, William McChesney Martin
      Jun 18- —So Much Force And So Little Peace: Dominican Republic
      Jun 20- [Korean War soldier over Lyndon Johnson's shoulder]: Vietnam War
      Jun 22- [Reappointment]
      Jun 23- [Dove on missile marked U.S. Viet Policy]: Vietnam War
      Jun 24- [World looks at a maternity ward]: birth rate
      Jun 25- [Unity, The New GOP]: Republican Party
      Jun 28- —One Order, We'll Done, Coming Up!: reapportionment
      Jun 29- Puppet Show: Vietnam War, China
      Jun 30- It Helps If You Shut Your Eyes On The Big Dips: stock market, economy
    - Jul 1965 (Oversize 2)
      Jul 1- Bon Voyage: tourism
      Jul 2- [Bird of the Month Wild Eyed Looney fringe]
      Jul 4- That Means It Isn't Murder—Just Voluntary Manslaughter: smoking
      Jul 7- Whose Side Are They On?: college students, Vietnam War, Ohio, New York, Missouri, Iowa
      Jul 8- [Common market]: Charles De Gaulle
      Jul 13- The Great Society: Lyndon B. Johnson
      Jul 14- [Mars closeups by Mariner IV]: space exploration
      Jul 16- Eclipse: Great Society, Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Jul 17- I Tell You, I Heard a Horn: space exploration, Soviet Union
      Jul 18- T-T-This Town Is B-Big Enough For Both of Us: American Football League, University of Miami
      Jul 20- I Saw People On It, But You Couldn't Call That Living: aliens
      Jul 21- Amateurs!: Internal Revenue Service, espionage
      Jul 22- We North Vietnamese Dress For These Freak Showers: peace, Vietnam War
      Jul 25- —Don't Always Look For The Silver Lining: currency
      Jul 27- We've Reached A Higher Level Of Discussion: nuclear weapons, disarmament
      Jul 28- [Step-up of War in Vietnam]: Vietnam War
      Jul 29- [Bird of the Month Kuku Kluck]: Ku Klux Klan
      Jul 30- [I Might Need You]: Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Aug 1965 (Oversize 2)
      Aug 3- Rabbit Ears: Gerald Ford, Vietnam War
      Aug 4- My, The Phenomena Are Restless Lately: UFOs, armed forces
      Aug 5- [voting Rights bill passed]: Abraham Lincoln, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Aug 6- —August 5, I Empted His Astray —: Lyndon B. Johnson
      Aug 8- —Har, Har, Hee Hee Hoo Hee Har, Ho Haw!: Medicare
      Aug 10- The Pacifist:
      Aug 11- Centaur: Greece
      Aug 12- I think It's Settling In: Vietnam War, Wayne Morse
      Aug 13- [War protest signs 1965, 1975, 1985, 1995]: Vietnam War, Hawaii, California, Philippines
      Aug 15- [Civil rights progress]: Los Angeles, Chicago, riots
      Aug 17- This Used To Be A Terrible Place To Live: Watts riots
      Aug 18- Records Were Made To Be Broken
      Aug 24- Ah Had To Shoot Him Sheriff, He Was Armed: civil rights, clergy
      Aug 25- Hey, Tower, Watch This Takeoff: Republican Party, Vietnam War
      Aug 26- I Like Some Bass When I Plan Peace Overtures: Vietnam War, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Aug 27- Watch The Riff-Raff Start Pouring In: immigration
    - Sep 1965 (Oversize 2)
      Sep 21- [The teachings of Gandhi]
      Sep 23- [Global War]: United Nations
      Sep 24- Headache: Asia, China
      Sep 26- Hitchhiker: right-wing politics, California, Republican Party
      Sep 28- One Of Us Must Get Through To The PTA Meeting: John Birch Society
      Sep 29- Home Stretch: Congress, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Sep 30- [Russian news stand]: Pravda, Izvestia, Wall Street Journal
    - Oct 1965 (Oversize 2)
      Oct 1- [You Are Now Leaving Hayneville Ala]: justice, Alabama
      Oct 5- If You Don't Like It Here, Feel Free To Lea—: Fidel Castro
      Oct 6- [United Nations as a baseball player]: India, Pakistan
      Oct 8- Gall Stone: Lyndon B. Johnson, Congress, right to work law
      Oct 10- Stand-In: Hubert Humphrey
      Oct 11- Report from Indonesia: Sukarno
      Oct 12- Rhodesia, Spirit of '65: racism, Ian Smith
      Oct 13- Well, Back To The Old Grind: Lyndon B. Johnson
      Oct 14- Oh, THAT!: Vietnam War
      Oct 17- [Fidel Castro with dog heading out to sea]: Cuba
      Oct17- You Look Kind Of Funny To Me, Welch: Barry Goldwater, Robert Welch
      Oct 18- Peace March: U.S. Flag
      Oct 19- —Burned His Credit Card By Mistake: protestors, draft
      Oct 21- I'll Keep you Posted: press, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Oct 22- Touchy Devils: HUAAC, Ku Klux Klan
      Oct 24- [89th Congress]: Lyndon B. Johnson
      Oct 25- [Metro—School Budgets Squeezing take of Property Owner]
      Oct 26- [Entering Hayneville, Ala]: Alabama, Ku Klux Klan
      Oct 28- Let Freedom Ring
      Oct 29- [Car with Brazil license plate]: democracy
      Oct 30- Aaaaaaaaaaagh! A Goblin!: UNICEF, right wing politics, Halloween
    - Nov 1965 (Oversize 2)
      Nov 1- [China sitting outside a door marked UN]: United Nations, China
      Nov 2- [Bird "Luci" locked in a cage]
      Nov 3- [Nelson Rockefeller]
      Nov 5- Some Candidates Kiss Babies: Charles De Gaulle
      Nov 7- Rhodesian Paper Doll: Ian Smith, Ku Klux Klan
      Nov 9- What Second Line?: inflation, aluminum industry, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Nov 10- GOOD Morning, Dear!: news
      Nov 11- [New York City blackout] (photograph pasted on a cartoon)
      Nov 14- [nationwide aluminum products]: Lyndon B. Johnson, aluminum industry
      Nov 16- [205th Free Cuba Commandos in Exile]
      Nov 18- They Don't Kick The Way They Used To: China, United Nations
      Nov 21- I Can Kill Anything Better Than You—Yah, Yah, Yah!: nuclear weapons, Russia
      Nov 23- [How the War went today]: Vietnam War casualties
      Nov 24- You Know Dear—I'll Bet A Man In Your Condition Could Get A Crack At The Heavyweight Champ: boxing
      Nov 26- [Growing Vietnam War casualties]
      Nov 28- Tshombe's Out, Tshombe's In! Mobutu This, Kasavubu That—Coup, Coup, Coup! I Tell You, Cheetah, This Place Ain't What It Used To Be: Congo, Moise Tshombe
      Nov 30- Blind Man's Bluff: Vietnam War, China
    - Dec 1965 (Oversize 2)
      Dec 3- W-Who Turned On That Light?: racism, civil rights, Anniston trial
      Dec 5- —I Had The Old Sleigh Up For A Dry Run, See? All Of A Sudden, WHOOSH! I Was Sideswiped By Two Guys Driving A Crazy, Metal-Plated Bottle!: Santa Claus
      Dec 7- [Charles De Gaulle]
      Dec 8- Let's Go Find a Cause: protestors
      Dec 10- Ga, Ga, Ga, Out Veet Num: Benjamin Spock, Vietnam War
      Dec 14- —Well, Hello, Chollie; It'd Be SO Nice To Have You Back Where You Belong, etc: Charles De Gaulle
      Dec 16- Dr. Livingston, I Presume: space exploration
      Dec 17- I'm Certain He Won't Let Himself Live Much Longer: Haydon Burns, Florida Legislature
      Dec 19- The Great Giveaway Program, Eh? Whatever Became Of Individual Initiative?: Santa Claus
      Dec 21- [Hanoi Peace bid]: Vietnam War
      Dec 22- [Made in the U.S.A.]: nuclear weapons
      Dec 24- Happy Holidays: U.S. Postal Service
      Dec 25- Who wants to worry about world problems today- Merry Christmas
      Dec- You're In Luck! I Found A Couple Of Seats On A Flight Leaving In 1983: Fidel Castro, Cuba
  - Undated
    - A (Oversize 2)
      The Act Is Dead!: elections, Robert King
      Admit It! You're Thinking Brutal Thoughts: New York City, police brutality
      —After The Trish In Haynesville, I Became Depressed And Developed A Nervous Twitch--: justice
      Agnes! You Know How The Big Boy Feels About That Kind Of Stuff': J. Edgar Hoover
      Agricultural Program: nuclear weapons, Russia
      [Aid To Rhodesia]: Ku Klux Klan
      All Clear?: right to work law
      Alliance for Progress: Argentina
      Altitude Record: food prices
      —And How Am I Today, Sweetie?: Lyndon B. Johnson, public opinion
      —And Now, A Question For Mayor Burns: Haydon Burns
      Angel: railroad industry, Lyndon B. Johnson
      Arc De Triomphe: Charles De Gaulle, Mao Zedong
      Arise!: China
      As I saw—er—see the situation, Goldwater...: Richard Nixon, Republican Party
      Atta Boy, Bill! I like A Good, Hard, Gutsy Campaign: Bill Miller, elections
    - A (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      —And Finally, Doctor, I Faced The Awful Fact That I'm the Only College Professor who doesn't know what to do ab out Vietnam: Vietnam War
      —And When I Come Home, Luci Baines, You'll Be There To Fetch My Pipe and Slippers: Luci Baines Johnson
    - B (Oversize 2)
      $$ Burns: Haydon Burns
      Baker Affair: Congress, Bobby Baker
      Barry Darling, If At Times I Seem Reticent...: Barry Goldwater, Republican Party
      Base Says They Are Not All Yankee Missiles!: sports
      Bay Pollution Control: pollution
      [Benjamin Franklin Bust Broken by a Football]
      Big Wheels: Jimmy Hoffa, Teamsters, Dave Beck
      The Bobby Baker Case: Bobby Baker, Congress
      Bobby's Baker: Bobby Baker
      Boktok: space exploration
      [Burns (porkchops)]: Haydon Burns
      [Burns Wind-up Doll]: Haydon Burns
    - B (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      Budget 1966: Lyndon B. Johnson (as the thinker)
    - C (Oversize 2)
      Call Detroit And Make Them Fix It: automobiles
      Campaign Maneuvers: Barry Goldwater, Republican Party
      Can Be Found Wandering in Southern United States: Republican Party, Democratic Party
      Captive Audience: crime, violence, television
      Captured U.S. Fliers
      The Cheerful Computer: Robert McNamara, Vietnam War, draft
      [CIA and Fulbright Committee]
      [Civil Rights (lilies)]
      [Civil Rights (Southern bloc)]
      Civil Rights, Sure—But Not Right Next Door: housing
      Cold War Strategy
      Congratulations, Lady, You've Been Liberated: Vietnam War
      Congress On The Move: taxes, government spending, defense
      Conquering the Aggressors: Congo
      Coup, Coup! Coup, Coup!: Latin America
    - C (oversize mounted) (Oversize 5)
      Can You Think Of Anything Else That Needs Shaping Up?: Republican Party, Gerald Ford, Everett Dirksen